{"question": "What is the difference between the predicted resources and the actual resources used?", "answer": "From one project to another, we want to minimize the difference between the predicted resources needed to complete a project and the actual resources used, including staff, equipment, and calendar time."}{"question": "What does the QA team do?", "answer": "This means they manage the testing of the software before it is released to customers."}{"question": "What is a filter for the software process?", "answer": "This are applied at various points during software engineering and serve to uncover errors and defects that can be removed."}{"question": "What is the definition of quality assurance?", "answer": "Quality assurance (QA) is the definition of process and the standards that should lead to high quality products and introduction of quality process into manufacturing process In software industry, different companies and industry sectors quality assurance is used in different ways; sometimes Q/A simply means the definition of procedures, processes and standards that are aimed at ensuring software quality is achieved."}{"question": "What is the definition of QA?", "answer": "In general, we would like to make sure our testing program covers a known percentage of the software, from one release to another."}{"question": "What is the definition of quality assurance?", "answer": "The list goes on and on."}{"question": "What is the definition of QA?", "answer": "How might a software development organization need to control variation?"}{"question": "Who is the author of this chapter?", "answer": "Chapter 9 QUALITY MANAGEMENT -Amir, Sudeep Rawal & Shristi Maharjan 9."}{"question": "What is the definition of quality management?", "answer": "1 Quality concept With development of software it is necessary to develop a concept."}{"question": "What is the meaning of the passage?", "answer": "(Our customers will likely be upset if the third release of a product has ten times as many defects as the previous release."}{"question": "What is the definition of quality assurance?", "answer": "9."}{"question": "What is the purpose of the chapter 9 QUALITY MANAGEMENT?", "answer": "Not only do we want to minimize the number of defects that are released to the field, we\u2019d like to ensure that the variance in the number of bugs is also minimized from one release to another."}{"question": "What is the definition of quality assurance?", "answer": "2 Quality Assurance The terms quality assurance is widely used in manufacturing industry."}{"question": "What is the definition of Q/A?", "answer": "In other cases Q/A also includes all configuration, management, verification and validation activities that are applied after a product has been handed over by a development team."}{"question": "What is a software review?", "answer": "3 SOFTWARE REVIEWS Software reviews is a \u201cfilter\u201d for the software process."}{"question": "What is the role of the QA team in software development?", "answer": "The QA team in most companies is responsible for managing the release testing process."}{"question": "What is the purpose of the article?", "answer": ") We would like to minimize the differences in speed and accuracy of our hotline support responses to customer problems."}{"question": "What is the definition of quality assurance?", "answer": "Software Quality Assurance encompasses > A quality management approach, > Effective software engineering technology (methods and tools), > Formal technical reviews that are applied throughout the software process, > A multitiered testing strategy, > Control of software documentation and the changes made to it, > A procedure to ensure compliance with software development standards (when applicable), and > Measurement and reporting mechanisms."}{"question": "What is the purpose of a formal technical review?", "answer": "At the end of the reviews all the attendees of FTR must decide whether to 1."}{"question": "What is the purpose of a formal technical review?", "answer": "Whether to accept the product without further modification."}{"question": "What is the purpose of a formal technical review?", "answer": "The FTR also serves to promote backup & continuing because number of people becomes familiar with parts of the software."}{"question": "What are the main objectives of a formal technical review?", "answer": "Review Meeting: Regardless of the FTR format that is chosen every meeting should abide by following constraints: > Between 3 to 5 people should be involved in review meeting > Advance preparation should occur but should be less than 2 hours of work for each person > The duration of the review meeting should not be more than 2 hours Given these constrains it should be obvious that an FTR focuses on a specific part of the overall software for example rather than attempting to review an entire design, walkthroughs are conducted for each components the individuals who has developed the work product \u2013 the producers- informs the project leader that the work product is complete and a review is required."}{"question": "What is the purpose of a formal technical review?", "answer": "> To achieve software that is developed in uniform manner."}{"question": "What is the purpose of a formal technical review?", "answer": "2."}{"question": "What is the purpose of a formal technical review?", "answer": "9."}{"question": "What is a formal technical review?", "answer": "4 FORMAL TECHNICAL REVIEWS A formal technical review is software quality activity performed by software engineers for following objectives; > To uncover error in function, logic or implementation for any representation of the software."}{"question": "What are the different ways that a review can be done?", "answer": "Reviews can be done in different ways."}{"question": "What is the purpose of a formal technical review?", "answer": "> To make projects more manageable."}{"question": "What is the most effective way to do a technical review?", "answer": "Reject the product due to several errors."}{"question": "What is the purpose of a formal technical review?", "answer": "Each FTR is conducted as meeting and will be successful only if properly planned, controlled, and attended."}{"question": "What is the purpose of a formal technical review?", "answer": "The project leader contacts a review leader who evaluates the product for readiness, generates copies of product materials and distributes it to two or three reviewers for advance preparation."}{"question": "What is the most effective filter form a quality assurance point?", "answer": "A formal technical review is the most effective filter form a quality assurance point."}{"question": "What is a formal technical review?", "answer": "An informal meeting around a coffee shop is a form of review, if technical problem are discussed."}{"question": "What is the purpose of a formal technical review?", "answer": "The reviewer including review leader reviews the product and establishes an agenda for the review meeting."}{"question": "What is the purpose of a formal technical review?", "answer": "> Verify software if it has met is requirement."}{"question": "What is the purpose of a formal technical review?", "answer": "After the review meeting one of the reviewer records the valid problems or errors that are discovered."}{"question": "What is the purpose of a formal technical review?", "answer": "In addition FTR serves as a training ground for junior engineers to observe different approach of software analysis, design and construction."}{"question": "What is a formal technical review?", "answer": "A formal presentation of software design to an audience of customers management and technical staffs is also form of review."}{"question": "What is the purpose of a formal technical review?", "answer": "> Ensure that software has been represented according to predefined standards."}{"question": "What are the requirements for a formal technical review?", "answer": "Review Guidelines Guidelines for conducting formal technical reviews must be established in advance all reviews, agreed upon and then followed: 1."}{"question": "What is the purpose of the review issue?", "answer": "The review issue is a single page form."}{"question": "What is the purpose of the FTR?", "answer": "2."}{"question": "What is the purpose of the FTR?", "answer": "9."}{"question": "What is the main purpose of the FTR?", "answer": "Review the product not the producer: > FTR should leave warm feeling of accomplishment."}{"question": "What is the FTR?", "answer": "> FTR must be kept on track and on schedule > FTR must be responsive and shouldn\u2019t be afraid to nudge people."}{"question": "What is the best way to conduct a formal review?", "answer": "5 Take written notes: It is good to make notes on wall board so that wording and priorities can be assessed by other reviewers;."}{"question": "What is the purpose of the review issue?", "answer": "The review issue serves two purposes: 1."}{"question": "How many people must be preparing for the FTR?", "answer": "6 Limit the number of participants and insist upon advance preparation: Number of people must be minimum and review team member must be preparing in advance."}{"question": "What is the purpose of the FTR?", "answer": "To serve an action item check list that guides the producer as correctness are made."}{"question": "What is the tone of the meeting?", "answer": "> Tone of meeting should be loose and constructive."}{"question": "What is the best way to conduct a formal review?", "answer": "Accept the product provisionally (with minor errors that could be correct but further additional review is not required."}{"question": "What should be the main focus of the training?", "answer": "The training should stress both issues and human Psychological side of review."}{"question": "What are the main points of the FTR?", "answer": "> What were the findings and conclusions?"}{"question": "What is the best way to conduct a formal review?", "answer": "Rather than spending time debating the question, the issue shouldn\u2019t be recorded for further discussion."}{"question": "What is the best way to conduct a review?", "answer": "9 Review your early review: Debriefing can be beneficial in uncovering problems with the review process itself."}{"question": "What is the purpose of the FTR?", "answer": "To identify the problem areas within the product."}{"question": "What is the purpose of the FTR?", "answer": "7 Develop a checklist for each product that is likely to be reviewer: A checklist helps the review leader to structure the FTR meeting and helps each to focus on important issues."}{"question": "What is the best way to conduct a formal review?", "answer": "> Errors should be pointed out gently."}{"question": "What is the best way to conduct a formal review?", "answer": "Set an agenda and maintain it."}{"question": "What is the purpose of the FTR?", "answer": "Review Reporting and Record Keeping During the FTR, a reviewer (the recorder) actively records all issues that have been raised."}{"question": "What is the best way to conduct a formal review?", "answer": "8 Conduct meaningful training for all review: For effective FTR all participants should receive training."}{"question": "What is the best way to conduct a formal review?", "answer": "3."}{"question": "Who did you review?", "answer": "> Who reviewed it?"}{"question": "What is the FTR summary report?", "answer": "In addition a FTR summary report is completed which answers 3 questions: > Who was reviewed?"}{"question": "What is the best way to conduct a formal review?", "answer": "4 Enunciate problems but don\u2019t try to solve every problem noted: Review is time for discussing related problems rather than solving problems instantly."}{"question": "What is the best way to conduct a formal review?", "answer": "3 Limit debate and rebuttal > When an issue is raised there may be universal agreement."}{"question": "What is the definition of reliability?", "answer": "Software reliability is not independent."}{"question": "What is the definition of a software quality assurance?", "answer": "The software can then behave unpredictably and produce unexpected outputs."}{"question": "What is the definition of a statistical quality assurance?", "answer": "> Once the vital few causes have been identified move to correct the problems that have caused the defects."}{"question": "What is the definition of a statistical quality assurance?", "answer": "> An attempt is made to trade each defect to its underlying cause."}{"question": "What is the definition of a statistical quality assurance?", "answer": "> Information about software defects is collected and categorized."}{"question": "What is the definition of reliability?", "answer": "9."}{"question": "What is the definition of a statistical quality assurance?", "answer": "A strict and detailed syntax and semantics ( meaning of words and sentences) can be defined for every programming language and a strict and detailed approach to the specification of the software requirement is required, if requirement and programming language can be represented in strict and detailed manner then we can apply mathematical proof of correctness to demonstrate that a program conforms exactly to its specifications."}{"question": "What is the definition of failure?", "answer": "Failure is non- conformance to the software requirement."}{"question": "What is the definition of a statistical quality assurance?", "answer": "As there are restrictions on costs and time the data is gathered carefully so that each data has some purpose and gets its expected precision."}{"question": "What is the definition of a formal SQA?", "answer": "Over past 2 decades software engineering community has argued for more formal SQA is required."}{"question": "What is the definition of statistical quality assurance?", "answer": "Once sufficient data or information is gathered, statistical studies are done."}{"question": "What is the definition of statistical quality assurance?", "answer": "Statistical samples are obtained from the software products to test for reliability of the software."}{"question": "What is the definition of a proof?", "answer": "proofs."}{"question": "Why are the tests limited?", "answer": "The tests are limited due to restrictions such as cost and time restrictions."}{"question": "What is the definition of reliability?", "answer": "Reliability: The probability of failure free operation over a specific time, in a given environment, for a specific purpose."}{"question": "What is the definition of statistical quality assurance?", "answer": "For software statistical quality assurance implies the following steps."}{"question": "What is the definition of a statistical quality assurance?", "answer": "After this phase, design of the software is stopped and the actual implementation phase starts."}{"question": "What is the definition of a failure?", "answer": "These may confuse and consequently stress the system operator."}{"question": "What is the definition of a failure?", "answer": "Hardware failure can generate spurious signals that are outside the range of inputs expected by the software."}{"question": "What is the definition of reliability?", "answer": "For reliability testing, data is gathered from various stages of development, such as the design and operating stages."}{"question": "What is the definition of reliability?", "answer": "7 Software reliability Ability: The probability that the system, at a point in time, will be operational and able to deliver the requested service."}{"question": "What is the definition of reliability?", "answer": "To achieve the satisfactory results from reliability testing one must take care of some reliability characteristics."}{"question": "How are time constraints handled?", "answer": "Time constraints are handled by applying fixed dates or deadlines for the tests to be performed."}{"question": "What is the definition of a proof of correctness?", "answer": "To prove programs correctness we can use Dijkistra and linger, mills and Witt etc."}{"question": "What is the definition of statistical quality assurance?", "answer": "6 STATISTICAL SOFTWARE QUALITY ASSURANCE Statistical is quality assurance reflects a growing trend throughout industry to become more quantitative about quality."}{"question": "How do you measure the quality of software?", "answer": "> Using the Pareto principle, isolate 20percent."}{"question": "What is the definition of a prediction model?", "answer": "Prediction modeling b."}{"question": "What are the three main components of software reliability?", "answer": "Assumptions 2."}{"question": "What are the three terms used in software metrics?", "answer": "9."}{"question": "What are the three terms used in software metrics?", "answer": "e."}{"question": "What is the definition of a prediction model?", "answer": "Estimation modeling These modeling techniques follow observation and analyzes with statistical inference."}{"question": "What are the three terms used in software metrics?", "answer": "1."}{"question": "What are the main attributes of software reliability?", "answer": "GOOD QUALITY, RELIABILITY AND MAINTAINABILITY ARE IMPORTANT ATTRIBUTES OF ENTERPRISE APPLICATIONS AND HAVE A HUGE IMPACT ON THE SUCCESS ON THE ECONOMICS OF THE BUSINESSES POWERED."}{"question": "What is the focus of the testing?", "answer": "if there are predefined deadlines), then intensified stress testing is used."}{"question": "What is the definition of a software model?", "answer": "Calendar time."}{"question": "What are the main components of software reliability?", "answer": "Many software models contain: 1."}{"question": "What is the definition of a framework for software metrics?", "answer": "A Framework for Software Metrics Measures, Metrics, and Indicators."}{"question": "What is the definition of a software model?", "answer": "Estimation Model Estimation model uses the current data from the current software development effort and doesn't use the conceptual development phases and can estimate at any time."}{"question": "What are the main components of the software model?", "answer": "They usually made prior development and regular test phases."}{"question": "What are the three terms used in software metrics?", "answer": "If the restrictions are on operation time or if the focus is on first point for improvement, then one can apply compressed time accelerations to reduce the testing time."}{"question": "What are the three main components of software reliability?", "answer": "Factors 3."}{"question": "What is the definition of a software model?", "answer": "operating time, 2."}{"question": "What is the focus of the testing?", "answer": "If the focus is on calendar time (i."}{"question": "What is the definition of software reliability?", "answer": "Mathematical function Software reliability can be divided into categories: a."}{"question": "What are the three types of models used for software reliability?", "answer": "They analyze previous data and some observations."}{"question": "What is the definition of a software model?", "answer": "The model follow the concept phase and the predication from the future time."}{"question": "What is a framework for software metrics?", "answer": "8 A framework for software metrics SOFTWARE METRIC IS A MEASURE OF SOME PROPERTY OF A PIECE OF SOFTWARE OR ITS SPECIFICATIONS."}{"question": "What is the definition of a software model?", "answer": "IT REALLY, REALLY MATTERS."}{"question": "What is the definition of a prediction model?", "answer": "Prediction Model This model uses historical data."}{"question": "What is the number of on off cycles?", "answer": "number of on off cycles, 3."}{"question": "What is the definition of a software model?", "answer": "There is no model which either complete or fully developed."}{"question": "What is the definition of a software model?", "answer": "There is no single model which can be used in every situation."}{"question": "what is the definition of reliability?", "answer": "Measurement of reliability in Mean Time between Failures (MTBF) MTBF=MTTF+MTTR Where, MTTF: Mean time to failure MTTR: Mean time to repair Ability= MTTF/(MTTF+MTTR)*100 Reliability= MTTF/(1+MTBF) Over 225 models have been developed since early 1970s, but how to quantify software reliability still remains unsolved."}{"question": "What are the main parts of the ISO 9126 standard?", "answer": "The standard is divided into four parts, which address, respectively, the following subjects: quality model; external metrics; internal metrics; and quality in use metrics."}{"question": "What is the definition of a quality measure?", "answer": "> Interpretation: The evaluation of metrics in an effort to gain insight into the quality of the representation."}{"question": "What is the definition of a quality measure?", "answer": "10 ISO Standard ISO 9126 is an international standard for the evaluation of software quality."}{"question": "What is the definition of quality?", "answer": "Quality Mode The quality model established in the first part of the standard, ISO 9126-1, classifies software quality in a structured set of characteristics and sub-characteristics."}{"question": "What are the definitions of the definition of a quality measure?", "answer": "These are also considered as nonfunctional requirements metrics."}{"question": "What is the definition of a quality model?", "answer": "> Feedback:Recommendations derived from the interpretation of product metrics and passed on to the software development team \u2013 9."}{"question": "What is the definition of a metric?", "answer": "9 Matrices for analysis and design model Metrics for the analysis > Functionality delivered \u2013 Provides an indirect measure of the functionality that is packaged within the software > System size \u2013 Measures the overall size of the system defined in terms of information available as part of the analysis model > Specification quality \u2013 Provides an indication of the specificity and completeness of a requirements specification Metrics for the Design Model > Architectural metrics \u2013 Provide an indication of the quality of the architectural design > Component-level metrics \u2013 Measure the complexity of software components and other characteristics that have a bearing on quality > Interface design metrics \u2013 Focus primarily on usability > Specialized object-oriented design metrics \u2013 Measure characteristics of classes and their communication and collaboration characteristics 9."}{"question": "What is the definition of a measure?", "answer": ", identification) of software measures and metrics appropriate for the representation of the software that is being considered > Collection: The mechanism used to accumulate data required to derive the formulated metrics > Analysis: The computation of metrics and the application of mathematical tools."}{"question": "What is the definition of a measure?", "answer": "e."}{"question": "What is the definition of a measure?", "answer": "* Measure :Provides a quantitative indication of the extent, amount, dimension, capacity, or size of some attribute of a product or process * Measurement: The act of determining a measure * Metric:(IEEE) A quantitative measure of the degree to which a system, component, or process possesses a given attribute * Indicator: A metric or combination of metrics that provides insight into the software process, a software project, or the product itself Activities of a Measurement Process > Formulation: The derivation (i."}{"question": "What is the definition of security?", "answer": "* Security \u2013 preventing unauthorized access to the software."}{"question": "What is a maintainability?", "answer": "* Behavior * Resource Behavior 5- Maintainability - A set of attributes that bear on the effort needed to make specified modifications."}{"question": "What is a function?", "answer": "1-Functionality - A set of attributes that bear on the existence of a set of functions and their specified properties."}{"question": "What is the definition of a function?", "answer": "Installability 7."}{"question": "What is the definition of a function?", "answer": "* Learnability * Understandability * Operability - ability to keep a system in a functioning and operating condition."}{"question": "What are the three maturity levels of a process?", "answer": "Processes are rated according to their maturity levels, which are defined as: Initial, Repeatable, Defined, Quantitatively Managed, and Optimizing."}{"question": "What is the definition of a function?", "answer": "3- Usability - A set of attributes that bear on the effort needed for use, and on the individual assessment of such use, by a stated or implied set of users."}{"question": "What is the definition of a function?", "answer": "Replaceability 8."}{"question": "What is a process improvement approach?", "answer": "11 CMM Capability Maturity Model Integration (CMMI) is a process improvement approach."}{"question": "What is the definition of a function?", "answer": "Changeability 5."}{"question": "What is the definition of a function?", "answer": "* Suitability * Accuracy * Interoperability \u2013 the capability of different programs to exchange data via a common set of exchange formats, to read and write the same file formats, and to use the same protocols * Compliance \u2013 the flexibility of the software to accept new features and enhancements."}{"question": "What is the definition of a function?", "answer": "6."}{"question": "What are the functions of a software program?", "answer": "The functions are those that satisfy stated or implied needs."}{"question": "What is the definition of reliability?", "answer": "2- Reliability - A set of attributes that bear on the capability of software to maintain its level of performance under stated conditions for a stated period of time."}{"question": "What is a CMMI?", "answer": "CMMI can be used to guide process improvement across a project, a division, or an entire organization."}{"question": "What is the definition of a functionality?", "answer": "* Maturity * Recoverability - software product can be modified in order to correct defects, meet new requirements, make future maintenance easier, or cope with a changed environment * Fault Tolerance - the property that enables a system (often computer-based) to continue operating properly in the event of the failure of (or one or more faults within) some of its components."}{"question": "What is the definition of a function?", "answer": "4- Efficiency - A set of attributes that bear on the relationship between the level of performance of the software and the amount of resources used, under stated conditions."}{"question": "What is the definition of a function?", "answer": "3."}{"question": "What is a portability?", "answer": "Testability 6- Portability - A set of attributes that bear on the ability of software to be transferred from one environment to another."}{"question": "What is the definition of a function?", "answer": "Adaptability 9."}{"question": "What is the definition of a function?", "answer": "Stability 4."}{"question": "What is the acronym for CMMI?", "answer": "Product and service acquisition \u2014 CMMI for Acquisition (CMMI-ACQ)."}{"question": "What is the definition of CMMI?", "answer": "g."}{"question": "What are the main sections of the plan?", "answer": "Initial sections describe the purpose and scope of the document and indicate those software process activities that are covered by quality assurance."}{"question": "What is the definition of CMMI?", "answer": "A CMMI model may also be used as a framework for appraising the process maturity of the organization."}{"question": "What is the name of the organization?", "answer": "By January of 2013, the entire CMMI product suite was transferred from the SEI to the CMMI Institute, a newly created organization at Carnegie-Mellon."}{"question": "What is the definition of CMMI?", "answer": "9."}{"question": "What does the word \"software\" mean?", "answer": "The word \"software\" does not appear in definitions of CMMI."}{"question": "What are the types of documents used in the CMMI plan?", "answer": ", ERDs, class hierarchies) \u2022 Technical documents (e."}{"question": "What is the definition of CMMI?", "answer": "1."}{"question": "What is the definition of CMMI?", "answer": "The documentation section describes (by reference) each of the work products produced as part of the software process."}{"question": "What is the definition of CMMI?", "answer": "It is not as specific to software engineering as its predecessor, the Software CMM."}{"question": "What is the purpose of the SQA plan?", "answer": "Developed by the SQA group, the plan serves as a template for SQA activities that are instituted for each software project."}{"question": "What is the definition of a CMMI?", "answer": ", project plan) \u2022 Models (e."}{"question": "What is the definition of a standard for SQA plans?", "answer": "A standard for SQA plans has been recommended by the IEEE."}{"question": "What is the meaning of CMMI?", "answer": "This generalization of improvement concepts makes CMMI extremely abstract."}{"question": "What are the three main sections of the CMMI plan?", "answer": "These include: \u2022 Project documents (e."}{"question": "What is the acronym for CMMI?", "answer": "Product and service development \u2014 CMMI for Development (CMMI-DEV), 2."}{"question": "What are the three main categories of CMMI?", "answer": "CMMI models provide guidance for developing or improving processes that meet the business goals of an organization."}{"question": "What is the management section of the plan?", "answer": "The management section of the plan describes SQA\u2019s place in the organizational structure, SQA tasks and activities and their placement throughout the software process, and the organizational roles and responsibilities relative to product quality."}{"question": "What is the name of the three acronyms?", "answer": "Service establishment, management, \u2014 CMMI for Services (CMMI-SVC), and 3."}{"question": "What is the definition of a CMMI plan?", "answer": "12 SQA plan The SQA Plan provides a road map for instituting software quality assurance."}{"question": "What are the documents noted in the SQA Plan?", "answer": "All documents noted in the SQA Plan are listed and all applicable standards are noted."}{"question": "What are the main components of the CMMI plan?", "answer": ", specifications, test plans) \u2022 User documents (e."}{"question": "What is the name of the CMMI?", "answer": "CMMI was developed by a group of experts from industry, government, and the Software Engineering Institute (SEI) at Carnegie Mellon University."}{"question": "What is CMMI?", "answer": "CMMI originated in software engineering but has been highly generalized over the years to embrace other areas of interest, such as the development of hardware products, the delivery of all kinds of services, and the acquisition of products and services."}{"question": "What is the minimum set of work products that are acceptable to achieve high quality?", "answer": "In addition, this section defines the minimum set of work products that are acceptable to achieve high quality."}{"question": "What are the standards, practices, and conventions section of the software certification plan?", "answer": "The standards, practices, and conventions section lists all applicable standards and practices that are applied during the software process (e."}{"question": "What is the definition of a certificate?", "answer": "It builds on existing software assurance, validation, and verification techniques but introduces the notion of explicit software certificates, which contain all the information necessary for an independent assessment of the demonstrated properties."}{"question": "What are the different types of certification?", "answer": "Software certification comprises a wide range of formal, semi-formal, and informal assurance techniques, including formal verification of compliance with explicit safety policies, system simulation, testing, code reviews and human \u201csign offs\u201d, and even references to supporting literature."}{"question": "What are the standards, practices, and conventions that are used during the software process?", "answer": ", document standards, coding standards, and review guidelines)."}{"question": "What is the definition of the minimum set of work products that are acceptable to achieve high quality?", "answer": "g."}{"question": "What are the requirements for the software engineering work?", "answer": "In addition, all project, process, and (in some instances) product metrics that are to be collected as part of software engineering42 work are listed."}{"question": "What is the definition of the test section?", "answer": "It also defines test record-keeping requirements."}{"question": "What is the definition of problem reporting and corrective action?", "answer": "Problem reporting and corrective action defines procedures for reporting, tracking, and resolving errors and defects, and identifies the organizational responsibilities for these activities."}{"question": "What is the purpose of the SQA Plan?", "answer": "The remainder of the SQA Plan identifies the tools and methods that support SQA activities and tasks; references software configuration management procedures for controlling change; defines a contract management approach; establishes methods for assembling, safeguarding, and maintaining all records; identifies training required to meet the needs of the plan; and defines methods for identifying, assessing, monitoring, and controlling risk."}{"question": "What can be the difference between the two types of certificates?", "answer": "Consequently, the certificates can have different types, and the certification process requires different mechanisms."}{"question": "What is the definition of a software certification?", "answer": "13 Software certification Software certification demonstrates the reliability and safety of software systems in such a way that it can be checked by an independent authority with minimal trust in the techniques and tools used in the certification process itself."}{"question": "What is the definition of a certificate?", "answer": "Certificates A certificate contains all information necessary for an independent assessment of the properties claimed for an artifact."}{"question": "What is the definition of the test section?", "answer": "The test section references the Software Test Plan and Procedure."}{"question": "What is the definition of the minimum set of work products that are acceptable?", "answer": "9."}{"question": "What is the approach for each review and audit?", "answer": "It provides an overview of the approach for each review and audit."}{"question": "What is the definition of the review and audits section?", "answer": "The reviews and audits section of the plan identifies the reviews and audits to be conducted by the software engineering team, the SQA group, and the customer."}{"question": "What is a release policy?", "answer": "A release policy formally describes under which conditions an artifact is deemed to be in an adequately certified state and can thus be released safely to another state."}{"question": "What is a release policy?", "answer": "Release Policies In the context of certification, a release refers to the transition of an artifact into a new defined state: for example, launch, system integration test, alpha and beta testing phases, spiral anchor-point milestones, or code inspection."}{"question": "What is the certification authority?", "answer": "g."}{"question": "What is the definition of a certification authority?", "answer": "Realistically, however, software development requires a wide range of notions of software reliability, safety, and validity, each with an appropriate certification authority."}{"question": "What is the internal structure of a system?", "answer": "The internal structure of a system is reflected in the certificate hierarchy."}{"question": "What are the types of certificates?", "answer": "Certifiable Properties and Certification Authorities Traditional V&V has only addressed a restricted range of formal properties."}{"question": "What types of artifacts are included in a certification?", "answer": ", product families, completed systems, individual components, or even code fragments) but also supporting non-software artifacts: requirements documents, system designs, component specifications, test plans, individual test cases, scientific and engineering data sets, and others."}{"question": "What are the two dimensions of a certificate?", "answer": "This structure is determined by two independent dimensions, (i) The system structure, and (ii) The certificate types."}{"question": "What is the certification authority?", "answer": "This must all be supported by a customizable SCMS."}{"question": "What are the types of artifacts that can be certified?", "answer": "Certifiable Artifacts Certifiable artifacts include not only the conventional software artifacts (e."}{"question": "What are the different types of certificates?", "answer": "Certificate Hierarchies The certificates for an artifact are not an unstructured collection but exhibit some hierarchical structure."}{"question": "What is the name of the authority?", "answer": "(iii) (iii) The certification authority."}